const prototypeData = [{	
	"id": 1,
	"question": "What movie is this from?: I like the way you die, boy.",
	"answers": ["Hateful Eight", "Django Unchained", "Toy Story 2", "The Good The Bad The Ugly"],
	"correctAnswer": "Django Unchained"
	}, {
	"id": 2,
	"question": "What movie is this from?: No Luke, I am your father.",
	"answers": ["Bugs life", "Star Wars", "Star Trek"],
	"correctAnswer": "Star Wars"
	}, {
	"id": 3,
	"question": "What movie is this from?: The cold never bothered my anyway.",
	"answers": ["The Titanic", "2012", "Frozen"],
	"correctAnswer": "Frozen"
	}, {
	"id": 4,
	"question": "What movie is this from?: You stay, I go, no following.",
	"answers": ["Lassy", "The Iron Giant", "Pain and Gain"],
	"correctAnswer": "The Iron Giant"
	}, {
	"id": 5,
	"question": "What movie is this from?: That's no moon.",
	"answers": ["Star Wars", "Star Trek", "Hitchikers Guide to the Galaxy"],
	"correctAnswer": "Star Wars"
	}, {
	"id": 6,
	"question": "What movie is this from?: I'M TIRED OF THESE MUTHAFUCKIN SNAKES ON THIS MUTHAFUCKIN PLANE!",
	"answers": ["Snakes on a Plane", "Anaconda", "Antz"],
	"correctAnswer": "Snakes on a Plane"
	}, {
	"id": 7,
	"question": "What movie is this from?: I just push people down and run away really fast!",
	"answers": ["Fast and Furious", "Justice League", "Man of Steel"],
	"correctAnswer": "Justice League"
	}, {
	"id": 8,
	"question": "What movie is this from?: That is americas ass",
	"answers": ["Ironman", "Mean Girls", "Avengers: End Game"],
	"correctAnswer": "Avengers: End Game"
	}, {
	"id": 9,
	"question": "What movie is this from?: Say adios to your jeuvos.",
	"answers": ["The Hateful Eight", "Super Bad", "True Grit"],
	"correctAnswer": "The Hateful Eight"
	}, {
	"id": 10,
	"question": "What movie is this from?: This house is a fucking prison! On planet bullshit!",
	"answers": ["Toy Story", "The Other Guys", "Step Brothers"],
	"correctAnswer": "Step Brothers"
	}, {
	"id": 11,
	"question": "Who is the main Bounty Hunter from Star Wars: Empire strikes back?",
	"answers": ["Jang Fett", "Boba Fett", "IG-88"],
	"correctAnswer": "Boba Fett"
	}, {
	"id": 12,
	"question": "Which American president is known to have visted Epsteins private sex island 26 times?",
	"answers": ["George Bush", "George Washington", "Bill Clinton"],
	"correctAnswer": "Bill Clinton"
	}, {
	"id": 13,
	"question": "Which country in the world is a back-to-back World War champion?",
	"answers": ["The U S of A baby", "Germany", "Australia"],
	"correctAnswer": "The U S of A baby"
	}, {
	"id": 14,
	"question": "I'm running out of questions for this dataset...",
	"answers": ["True", "False"],
	"correctAnswer": "True"
	}, {
	"id": 15,
	"question": "What gets shorter the longer it lives?",
	"answers": ["Pencile", "Candle", "Me", "All of the above"],
	"correctAnswer": "All of the above"
	}, {
	"id": 16,
	"question": "What movie is this from?: There are things that go bump in the night, we are the ones who bump back.",
	"answers": ["Annabelle", "Ghost Busters", "Hellboy"],
	"correctAnswer": "Hellboy"
	}]
	
	module.exports = {
	prototypeData
	}